[{
	"question": "When does Kenya celebrate Independence Day?",
	"options": ["A. 15th August", 
		"B. 12th December", 
		"C. 26th January", 
		"D. 4th July"],
	"answer": "B. 12th December"
},
{
	"question": "Nobel prize is awarded for which of the following disciplines?",
	"options": ["A. Literature, peace and economics", 
		"B. Medicine or Physiology", 
		"C. Chemistry and Physics", 
		"D. All the above"],
	"answer": "D. All the above"
},

{
	"question": " You have noticed a potential victim and ensured the scene is safe. What is your next step?",
	"options" : [ "A. Begin chest compressions",	
	"B. Check for victim's responsiveness",
	"C. Call the victim's doctor",
	"D. Provide rescue breathing"],

	"answer": "B. Check for victim's responsiveness"
},

{
	"question": " Who is the father of Computer science?",
	"options" : [ "A.George Washington",	
	"B. Earl Nightingale",
	"C.Charles Babbage",
	"D. Abraham Lincon"],

	"answer": "C. Charles Babbage"
},
{
	"question": " In which type of computer, data are represented as discrete signals?",
	"options" : [ "A.Digital Computer",	
	"B. Super Computer",
	"C.Abbacus",
	"D. Hybrid Computer"],

	"answer": "A. Digital Computer"
},
{
	"question":	"World War I began in which year?",
	"options" : [ "A. 1923",
"B. 1938",
"C. 1917",
"D. 1914"],

"answer": "D. 1914"

},

{
	"question":	"Adolf Hitler was born in which country?",
	"options" : [ "A. France",
"B. Germany",
"C. Austria",
"D. Hungary"],

"answer": "C. Austria"

},

{
	"question":	"Where was John F. Kennedy assassinated in?",
	"options" : [ "A. New York",
"B. Austin",
"C. Dallas",
"D. Miami"],

"answer": "C. Dallas"

},

{
	"question":	"The first successful printing press was developed by this man? ",
	"options" : [ "A. Johannes Gutenberg",
"B. Benjamin Franklin",
"C. Sir Isaac Newton",
"D. Martin Luther"],

"answer": "A. Johannes Gutenberg"

},


{
	"question":	"In 1594, William Shakespeare joined the company of this London theatre.    ",
	"options" : [ "A. Broadway",
"B. Oxford University Theatre",
"C. The Globe",
"D. The London Palladium"],

"answer": "D. The London Palladium"

},


{
	"question":	"The United States bought Alaska from which country?  ",
	"options" : [ "A. Japan",
"B. China",
"C. Russia",
"D. Denmark"],

"answer": "C. Russia"

},


{
	"question":	"What technology is used to record cryptocurrency transactions?  ",
	"options" : [ "A. Digital wallet",
"B. Mining",
"C. Blockchain",
"D. Token"],

"answer": "C. Blockchain"

},

{
	"question":	"What technology is used to make telephone calls over the Internet possible? ",
	"options" : [ "A. NFC",
"B. Bluetooth",
"C. Ethernet",
"D. VoIP"],

"answer": "D. VoIP"

},

{
	"question":	"What is the term for text that automatically continues from one line to the next? ",
	"options" : [ "A. Word processing",
"B. Word wrapping",
"C. Word flowing",
"D. Word binding"],

"answer": "B. Word wrapping"

},

{
	"question":	"Which computer language is the most widely used?",
	"options" : [ "A. C#",
"B. Swift",
"C. PHP",
"D. Java "],

"answer": "A. C#"

},

{
	"question":	"What was the first cross-platform PDF software?",
	"options" : [ "A. Adobe Acrobat",
"B. Foxit PhantomPDF",
"C. Nitro Pro",
"D. Nitro Pro"],

"answer": "A. Adobe Acrobat"

}






]
